SARATH LALK

CRT MANAGER

- KALLINGAL(H), THENHIPALAM P O, MALAPPURAM MALAPPURAM, KL, 673636
- 956 785 7073
- SARATHLALKALLINGAL@GMAIL.CO M

Highly motivated and positive individual with great organizational and communication skills. Very much interested in customer interaction and community building. Customer service master and efficient problem solver. Deftly manage administrative functions of the practice. Provide thorough answers and solutions and provide an exceptional customer experience. Handling motorcycle sales, coordinating rides, riding gears and apparel sales, service advising etc. Have a huge community and contact with well known riders and motorcycle enthusiastic peoples across Kerala. Attended Ridermania - national event of the brand Royal Enfield- for 3 times. Also holds the credit of 2nd highest registrations done for Ridermania in 2019.





Work History

2016-06 - Current

CRT MANAGER

BLUEMOUNTAIN AUTOS-Royal Enfield, KOZHIKODE, KERALA

- Operated with high integrity, built trust, and earned sustained credibility with internal and external clientele
- Community building
- Conducting rides with customers in every weekends
- Invite and make them participate into various events conducted by the company, like Reunion, Ridermania, Himalayan oddessey etc
- In charge of sales of motorcycle accessories, riding gear, apparels
- Frequently making business of riding gears and apparels for 50k per month
- Also service and spares 20k per month
- Attended Ridermania-biggest yearly event of Royal Enfield for 3 times as an official
- Done 76 individual registrations for Ridermania 2019, which is all time 2nd highest in Kerala

2016-01 - 2016-06

2014-10 - 2015-05

Sales Executive

Bluemountain Autos-Royal Enfield, Kozhikode, Kerala

- Sales consultant
- Activity and demo coordinating
- Achieved target frequently

Sales Executive

Popular Motors, Ramanattukara, Kerala

- Sales consulting
- Demo and activities at various places



Education

2011-06 - 2014-03

Diploma in Automobile Engineering: Automotive Engineering

KMCT Polytechnic College - Kalanthode, Mukkom

2008-08 - 2010-07

Auto Electrical And Electronics : Automotive Engineering Technology

Model ITI - Kozhikode

2006-06 - 2008-03

High School Diploma

Model HSS - Calicut university campus



Languages

English





Place: Kozhikode

Date: SARATH LAL. K